BERK GÜMÜŞ

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT

+90 507 420 8277

brkgums@gmail.com
Ankara, Türkiye
Personal website (Work notes)

LANGUAGE

Türkçe (Native) English (B2)

SKILLS

ASP.NET Web Api, Spring Boot, React Native, Next.js, jQuery, DevExpress, C#, JavaScript, Fast Report, Design Thinking, Jira

CERTIFICATIONS

University of Alberta-Software Architecture (2024.06) EF SET English Certificate B2(2024.05) Board INFINITY-ASP.NET Web API course (2024.05) Udemy-Complete Data Science Bootcamp (2022.10) Global AI Hub-Introduction to Machine Learning (2022.06)

EDUCATION

Kirikkale University
2018-2024
BA in Computer Engineering
- Theatre Club

Politechnika Lubelska 2022-2023 Erasmus in Computer Science

REFERENCE

Wiser Sense Kerem TOKER Software Team Lead Contact: can be sent upon request

PROFILE

With a year of professional experience and 4 years of self-development, I've built skills in software engineering. I'm currently developing websites using ASP.NET Web API, Spring Boot, React and especially Spring boot.

I adapt quickly to new technologies and excel in problem-solving. I'm committed to continuous learning and contributing to innovative projects in the IT sector.

EXPERIENCE

TertuliaTalks-Full-stack developer and startup leadership (co-founder)

2024.06- sti

Involving volunteers' developers in the process and acting as mentor. Startup establishment stages, preparation of the development process, CI/CD process management, team management.

Wiser sense - Junior Full-stack software developer (Part-time)

2023.06-2024.05

Developed a web application using ASP.NET Web Api and Devextreme technologies for 4 months.

Test Engineer (Part-time)

3 months of manual testing and wrote test automation with JavaScript selenium library.

Junior Mobile Developer (Intern)

3 months of mobile application development with .net Maui and React Native technologies (mostly React Native)

Zirve-Software Engineer (Intern)

2021.07-2021.08

Worked with ASP.NET Boilerplate framework.

Başarsoft -Software Engineer (Intern)

2019.07-2019.08

Worked as a volunteer with HTML CSS technologies.

PROJECT

Tertulia Talks - co-founder, full stack developer | <u>GitHub</u> <u>Web Site</u> Technologies: TypeScript (React, Next.js), ASP.NET Web API, Azure, PostgreSQL.

Stock Prediction Application -full stack developer | <u>GitHub</u> <u>Werb Site</u> Technologies: Data Mining with JavaScript (Selenium), backend with ASP.NET, frontend with React, and Neon Tech cloud database.

E-Commerce API - Backend developer | GitHub

Technologies: Spring Boot